<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lab 4 Challenge</string>
    <string name="buttonText_one">Text One</string>
    <string name="buttonText_two">Text One</string>
    <string name="buttonText_three">Text One</string>
    <string name="displayText_one"> How Stupid I am and Reasons Why You Shouldn’t Accept Me
Dear admission officer, I know it will be a boring essay for you if I tell you about how sad my life is and I didn’t want to brag about how brilliant I am either. So, to catch your attention, I have decided to write an essay about how stupid I am and reasons why you shouldn’t accept me into your school.
In my first semester on primary school. I was ranked 48th out of 60 students but surprisingly, I was 15th the next semester and 7th in my third semester.
        Since then I keep improving myself until now on my last year of senior high school, I am the first in my class. I don’t mean to show off but I can’t really resist the temptation because I worked my way out all the way from the bottom to this point. I’m not brilliant, my intelligence isn’t innate then why should you have me as student in your school?
 </string>
    <string name="displayText_two">Secondly, in my school, all students with good grades will be offered to be moved into international classes where studying is being conducted bilingually which is in Indonesian and in English. A student can only be offered this opportunity twice for the whole 3 years of senior high school. I was offered this chance twice but I rejected both of them. People say it is stupid decision. I make poor decision then why admit me into your school?…show more content…
Every football lover’s dream is to be a football player and so do I. Somehow, I’m a really bad football player that all
        my teammates said that I was a “black hole” in their team. I am the weakest point on the field that our opponent can
        exploit and take an advantage of.</string>
    <string name="displayText_three">
            There are far too many idiot\'s reproducing in our society. Stupid people are
             becoming an epidemic to this world. The act of those people having sex is of no concern
             or harm to me, but the children that are produced due to this only add to the number in the
             slack-jawed, drooling populous that is slowly beginning to drain our society.
             I suggest that the government make an I.Q. test mandatory for couples applying
             for a marriage license. If the test results are low enough, refuse the licensee until they
             have both been successfully sterilized. It is a privilege to have children, sometimes, but
             still not just anyone should be allowed to breed successfully.
    </string>
</resources>